A Guide to the Alfred E. Cohn papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA132
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1
  - Chamberlain, Joseph P., 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Chamberlain, J.P. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Chambers, Robert, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Chambers, Robert (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - de la Chapelle, Clarence E., 1945 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Chaplin, Walter, 1940 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Chalfonte-Haddon Hall, 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Chesney, Alan M., 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Chickering, H.T., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - China Society of America, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Chisholm, George B., 1945 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Christie, Loring C., 1940-1940 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - The Churchman, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Clark, Jane Perry, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Clark, Grenville, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Clark, W. Irving, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Clinical Abstracts, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Cohn, Peter A. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Craig, Emma, 1923-1927 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Conner, Lewis A., 1923 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Cushing, Harvey, 1926 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Canfield, Cass, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Carlile, Julian A., 1953 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Chamberlain, Samuel, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Chambers, Robert, 1947-1949 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Chanutin, Alfred, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Chase, Harry Woodburn, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Cheer, S.N., 1947 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Chen, K.K., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Childs, Richard S., 1947 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Chirgerman, Samuel, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Clark, D.G., 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Clark, Grover Mrs., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Clinch, Edward S., 1949-1950 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Christian, Henry A., 1951 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - China Medical Board, 1940-1942 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Cocklin, Mr., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cohen, Ben V., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cohen, Ben V. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cohen, Ira, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cohen, Ira (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cohen, Morris R., 1943 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cohn, Alfred, 1941-1945 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Coleman, Milton L., 1943 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Conners, E.J., 1945 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cook, Alfred A., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cook, Herman J., 1940 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cooke, Morris L., 1943 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cohen, J.G., 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Cohn, Theodore D., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Cowdry, E.V., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Coburn, Alvin F., 1932 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Cochran, Arthur Mrs., 1935 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Cohen, Joseph and Mrs., 1932 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Cohen, Morris R., 1929-1934 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Cohn, Alfred and Mrs., 1928-1935 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Collège de France, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Collip, J.B., 1931 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Columbia Grammar School, 1932-1935 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Columbia University, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Columbia University Press, 1928 1934 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Comrie, John D., 1928 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Concialdi, Lewis B., 1928 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Conklin, Viola P., 1929 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Conant, James B., 1933 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Conner, Lewis A., 1928-1935 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Conner, Lewis A. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Cook, E. Fullerton, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Cook, Thomas & Sons, 1927-1935 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Cooke, Stenson Sir, 1933-1934 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Cooper, Viola Irene (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Copeland, Royal S., 1929 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Copeland, Royal S. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Columbia University, 1946 1950-1953 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Commonwealth Fund, 1940-1945 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Costello, Bill, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Costello, Bill, 1945-1946 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Coca, Arthur F., 1924 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Cohn Dr. ca, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Cohen, Morris R., 1924 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Cobb, Stanley (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Coggeshall, Lowell T., 1938 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Cohen, Benjamin V., 1937-1938 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Cohen, Morris R., 1937 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Cohn, Alfred E., 1938 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Cohn, Leonard A. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Collinson, John, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Columbia Grammar School, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Conner, Lewis A., 1936-1937 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Cook, Herman J., 1936-1939 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Columbia University, 1924-1925 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Corcoran, Thomas, 1936 1939 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Cook, Walter W.S., 1939 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Corwin, E.H.L., 1939 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - CoTui, Frank, 1937-1939 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Country Gentleman, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Cowdry, E.V., 1936 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Crawford, J. Hamilton, 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Crowe, S.J., 1937 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Cumming, H.S., 1936 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Cummings, C.E., 1936 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Curran, J.A., 1936 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Curran, J.A. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Current Titles from Biological Journals, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Cutler, Edith M., 1939 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Cowdry, E.V., 1925-1927 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Crawford, J. Hamilton, 1923-1927 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Cushing, Harvey, 1925 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Cori, Carl F., 1933 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Corner, George W., 1932 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Corscaden, James A., 1933 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Cosgrave, Millicent, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - CoTui, Frank, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Councilman, Elizabeth, 1930 1933 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Cowdry, E.V., 1930-1931 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Cowdry, E.V. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Craig, Stuart L., 1933 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Craig, Rufus B. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Crampton, C. Ward (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Crawford, J. Hamilton, 1928 1930 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Crawford, Sir Raymond, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Cullen, Glenn E., 1930 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Cushing, Harvey (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Customs, U.S., 1931 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Cutler, Elliott, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Corning, H.K., 1941 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Corwin, E.H.L., 1941 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Coster, Vinanza Mrs., 1942 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Cotrim, Nelson, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Cowdry, E.V., 1941-1942 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Craig, Frank, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Crawford, J. Hamilton, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Crawford, J.H. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Crow, Carl, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Crutcher, K.G., 1941 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Curner, Edward Charles, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Cutler, Condict W., 1943 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Corvan, Jerome, 1950-1954 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Corwin, E.H.L., 1946 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Cotton, T.F., 1946 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Cousins, Norman, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Cowles, John Jr., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Cowles, Russell and Mrs., 1949 1953 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Craig, Howard Reid, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Crampton, C. Ward, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Crosby, Irene, 1949 1952-1953 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Cypress Gift House, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Cushing, Harvey, 1928-1929 1933-1935 1939 undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Dexter, Richard, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Dieterich, Conrad A., 1923-1924 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Dieuaide, Francis R., 1923 1925-1927 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - d'Irsay, Stephen, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Digest of Treatment, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Danish Freedom and Democracy, American Friends of, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Davich, M., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Davenport, Russell, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Davis, Abraham M., 1944 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Davidson, Jo, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Davis, Charles, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Davis, Harriet Eager, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Davis, Michael M., 1940 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Dawson, Martin D. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Deering, Olive, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - De Graff, Arthur C. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Dempsey and Carroll, 1940 1943 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - de Kruif, Paul, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Dickerson, B.J., 1943 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Diethelm, Oskar, 1942 1945 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Dieuaide, Francis R., 1940-1942 1945 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Davidson, William, 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Davis, Alex, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Davis, Lambert, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Davis, Paul H., 1948 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Day, Raymond and Roselle, 1946-1948 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - de Aguilar, Victoria Salas, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Décarie, Thérèse, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - De Hahn, Dorothea, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - de Iongh, Mrs. Daniel Crena, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - De Silver, Margaret, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - de Jager, P. and Sons, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Derwin, James F., 1948 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Desmond, Thomas C., 1947-1950 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Diamond, Henry R., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Dieuaide, Francis R., 1948 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Dittenhoefer, Henry T., 1948 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Daly, I. de Burgh, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Dally, J.F. Halls, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Daniel, J., 1928 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Davis, Alex, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Davis, Michael M., 1929-1930 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Dawson, M.H., 1935 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - de Laguna, Theodore, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - DeMoor, Jean, 1933 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Deonna, Waldemar, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - De Porte, J.V., 1930 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Derow, H.A., 1930 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Dewey, John, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Dieuaide, Francis R., 1928-1935 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Dieuaide, F.R. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - d'Irsay, Stephen, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Danzis, Max, 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Davenport, John, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Davis, Thomas K., 1937 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Dauber and Pine Bookshops, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Dawson, M.H. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - DeGraff, Arthur C., 1938-1939 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - de la Chapelle, Clarence E., 1936-1939 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Democracy, Friends of, 1929 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Denman, Helen, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Derryberry, Mayhew, 1939 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Dexter, Richard, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Dick, G.F. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Diehl, C.H., 1936 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Dieuaide, F.R. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Dieuaide, Francis R., 1948 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Dobsevage, I. George, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Donnelly, Lucy, 1924 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - du Noüy, P., 1923 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Dublin, Louis I., 1924 1926-1927 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Doe, Janet (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Draper, George, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Dublin, Louis I., 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Deyrup, Natalie Johnson, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Dochez, A.P., 1951 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Dole, Vincent P., 1949 1951 1953 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Dothard, Robert L., 1946-1947 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Doyle, Joseph, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Drew, Georgina M., 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Drinker, Cecil L., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Dube, Norman, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Duffus, R.L., 1947 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Drury, Betty, 1946-1947 1950 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Democracy, Friends of, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Dunn, Halbert L., 1947 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Duggan, Stephen, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Dunham, Edward K., 1950-1953 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Dutton, E.P. and Co., Inc., 1947 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Dublin, Louis P., 1946 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Dziewatkowski, D.D., 1951 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Dochez, A.R., 1935 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Dock, George, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Donnelly, Lucy, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Dornan, William J., 1928 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Drinker, Cecil K., 1930 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Drischell, Doris C., 1934 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Dublin, Amos, 1931 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Dublin, Louis I., 1929-1935 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Dublin, Louis I. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Du Bois, E.F., 1931 1934 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Duel, Arthur, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Duggan, Stephen, 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Dunn, Herbert L., 1929 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Dwelly, E., 1928 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Dochez, A.R., 1944 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Dochez, A.R. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Dock, William, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Documents, Superintendent of, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Doering, Anne M., 1944 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Douvran?, Catherine ca, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Doty, Edward T., 1940 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Drury, Betty, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Dublin, Louis I., 1941 1943-1944 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Dublin, Louis I. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Dublin, Thomas D., 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Du Bois, Eugene F., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Dubos, René, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Dunbar, Flanders, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Dunn, Halbert L., 1940 1944 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Dodge, Katherine G., 1943 circa 1940 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Documents, Superintendent of, 1946-1949 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Doe, Janet, 1949-1953 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Douglas, Paul H., 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Ecker, Lewis C., 1936 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Ecker, Lewis C. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Enrich, Edward Price, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Erich, William E., 1937-1938 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Elkins, Elisabeth R., 1936 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Elkins, Abram I., 1937 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Ellicott, Nancy, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Ellis, A.W.M., 1936 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Ellsworth, Mrs. Allison B., 1937 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Erdmann, Martin, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Erdmann, William and Mrs, 1936-1938 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Erving, Emma L., 1938 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Erstein, Benedict, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Ehrich, A., 1926 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Ehrich, N.S., 1924 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Enrich, William J., 1926 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Ellis, Arthur, 1924 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Emerson, Haven (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Erlanger, Abraham, 1925 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Erskine, John (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Ettinger, N., 1927 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Earl, Ivan H., 1942 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Echareves Press, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Ehrich, William, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Eliot, Ellsworth, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Ellicott, Miss, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Elliot, Huger, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Ellis, Arthur, 1941 1944 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Elman, Anne [re], 1941 1946 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Elwood, Everett S., 1940 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Embree, Edwin R., 1941 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Embree, Edwin (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Emerson, Haven, 1940 1944 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Emerson, Kendall, 1941-1941 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Erdmann, Mrs. William, 1940 1944 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Erlanger, Joseph, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Erskine, John, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Evans, Luther H., 1945 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Evans, Margaret B., 1944 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Edmunds, C.W., 1932 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Ebeling, Albert H., 1930 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Edsall, David L., 1934 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Edwards, D.J., 1928 1930-1931 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Eggleston, Margery K., 1928 1934 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Ehrich, H.L., 1932 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Ehrich, Mrs., 1932 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Ehrich, W.E., 1930-1932 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Ehrlich, Elias H., 1933-1934 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Eller, J.J. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Ellicott, N.P., 1931-1933 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Elliman, Douglas L. and Co., 1930 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Elliot, Huger, 1929-1930 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Ellis, A.W.M., 1931 1935 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Ellis, A. Caswell, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Elting, Arthur W., 1928 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Emerson, Haven, 1928 1932-1934 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Engler, A.C., 1935 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Eppinger, Hans, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Erdmann, Annette W., 1929-1930 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Erdmann, Martin, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Erdmann, Jule, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Erdmann, William, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Ernst, Bernard, 1934-1935 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Europa, S.S., 1931 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Evans, CA. Lovatt, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Evening Post, New York, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Eastman Kodak Co., 1951 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Ehrich, Wilhelm, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - data and graphs, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Eckenhoff, J.E., 1946 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - The Economist, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Eder, Howard A., 1947 1952 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Education, U.S. Office of, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Ehrich, W., 1946 1952 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Eisenmenger, William J., 1953 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Ellis, Arthur, 1946-1947 1953 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Ellis, Kay, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Emerson, Haven, 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Endeavour, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Epler, Mrs. Curtis, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Erskine, John (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Erskine, Mrs. John, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Excerta Medica, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Falk, John, 1937 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Farkas, Prof., 1939 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Feder, Janet, 1939 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Findlay, Francis M., 1936-1937 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Findley, S.W. (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Fine, Jacob (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Fincken, William C., 1939 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Fishbein, Morris, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Flinn, W., 1937-1939 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Fairchild Aerial Surveys, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Farmer Bureau Inc., 1946 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Farrar, Straus and Young, 1947-1952 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Fassett, James, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Federations of Jewish Philanthropies of New York, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Feil, Harold, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Finch, Edith, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Fine, Jacob, 1951-1952 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Film Foundation, International, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Finkelstein, Louis, 1946-1947 1952 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Fitz, Reginald, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Fleissner, Else M., 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Flexner, Abraham, 1943 1950 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Flexner, Helen, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Fluorescent Service Co., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Faber, Knud, 1923-1926 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Feil, Harold, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Ferrell, John A., 1923 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Fine, M.S., 1924 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Finkle, Philip, 1923 1925 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Fister, O., 1925 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Flexner, Jacob A., 1923-1925 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Flexner, Washington, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Frank, Morris J., 1926 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Fahr, George, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Fay, Frank, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Feil, Harold, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Felkin, E., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Ferguson, John, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Ferris, John P., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Field, Marshall, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Fine, Jacob, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Finer, Mrs. Herman, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Finkelstein, Louis, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Finletter, Thomas K., 1944 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Finnerty, Francis A., 1944 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Fishbein, Morris, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Fisher, Sterling, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Fitzgerald, Marietta, 1944-1945 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Flagler, Harry Harkness (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Flexner, Helen, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Flinn, Waldo R., 1940-1945 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Faber, Knud, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Falk, Henry C., 1928 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Farrel, Franklin Jr. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Fenichel, Nathan M., 1930 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Finkle, Philip, 1928-1934 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Finney, J.M.T., 1932 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Fischer, Dr., 1931 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Fishbein, Morris, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Fishberg, Arthur M., 1931 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Fitz, Reginald, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Flexner, Jean, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Flexner, Helen, 1930 1935 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Flexner, William, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Flexner, Jacob, 1929-1932 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Flexner, Jennie M., 1930 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Fliess, R., 1933 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1941-1942 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Fowler, Dorothy Canfield, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Foy, Mabel (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Frank, Lawrence K. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Frank, Lawrence K., 1944-1945 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Fraser, Sir Ian, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Frazier, Chester N. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Fremont-Smith, D.F. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Fremont, R.E., 1944 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - French, Isabel, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Frank, Angelika W., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Fry, Varian, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Fülöp-Miller, René, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Furlong, Thomas, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Frohnmayer, Charles, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Futcher, Palmer H., 1940 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Fellows, H.H., 1944 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Fischer, L.B. Inc., 1942-1943 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Fischer, Walther, 1928-1935 (Box 9, Folder 6-8)
  - Fifth Avenue Bank, 1946-1953 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Flexner, Bernard, 1942 1944 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Flory, Curtis M., 1948 1950 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Flinn, Waldo R., 1946 1949-1951 1954 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Friedenwald, Jonas S., 1946 1948 1950 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Ford Foundation, 1951-1953 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Fosburgh, James W. Mrs., 1948-1953 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Foreign Relations, Council on, 1946-1949 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Flexner, Simon, 1939 1946 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1945-1949 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Fischer, Walther, 1921-1930 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Foster, Albert D., 1943 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Foster, G.S., 1923 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Francis, W.W., 1929 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Fraser, Francis R., 1921-1923 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Fredericq, Henri, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Foerster, Robert F. and Lilian H., 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Ford, Eleanor J., 1928-1929 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1934-1935 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Foster, Lawrence, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Fox, Howard, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Fox, Howard (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - France, Melville J., 1929-1933 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Franchini, Guiseppe, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Francis, W.W., 1929 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Frank, Jerome, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Frank, Morris J., 1928 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Frank, Parda, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Frank, Robert T., 1932 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Frankel, Lee K., 1931 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Frank, Morris J., 1928 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Frankfurter, Marion, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Franklin, Kenneth, 1934 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Francis, W.W., 1932 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Fraser, Francis R. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Fraser, Francis R., 1930-1933 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Frazier, Chester N., 1932 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Fredericq., Walter, 1935 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Freud, Prof (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Fried, Minna, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Friedenberg, Walter, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Friedenwald, Jonas S., 1929 1931 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Frissell, L.F., 1929 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Fulton, Frank T., 1932 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Fulton, John F., 1933 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Fortune, Kathryn [re], 1939 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1936 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Fox, Herbert, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Frank, Lawrence K., 1939 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Fraser, Francis R., 1936 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Fremont-Smith, Dr. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Forkner, Claude E., 1939 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Foucar, F.H., 1937 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Futcher, P.H., 1939 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Frank, Lawrence K., 1937 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Fraser, Francis R., 1937-1938 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Friedenwald, Jonas, 1938 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Friedman, E.D., 1937 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Frissell, Lewis Fox, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Fülöp-Miller, René, 1936 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Fulton, John F., 1939 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Forkner, Claude E., 1951 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Foss, Oliver [re], 1946 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Foster, W.N., 1952 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Fox, Leon A., 1953 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Frankel, Charles, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Frederick, Arthur, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 9)